Arts and Sciences and Engineering Bulletins UP006
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Arts and Sciences and Engineering Bulletins
1942 -- 2021
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Engineering
School of Arts and Sciences
School of the Museum of Fine Arts
UP006
3.9 Linear Feet
56 Volumes
55 Digital Object(s)
239.59 Megabytes Of the 55 digital objects in this collection, 41 have extent information and comprise 239.59 MB.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by Tufts Technology Services, 2011 -- 2021.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into four series: Arts and Sciences, Engineering, and SMFA Bulletins; Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Bulletins; Announcement of courses and course descriptions; and Summer School Bulletins.
Related Materials
Tufts Combined Catalogs, Bulletins and Course Announcements, 1854-1970. Tufts University. Digital Collections and Archives. Medford, MA.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of the catalogs and bulletins from 1970 to the present for the School of Arts and Sciences and the School of Engineering, both at the undergraduate and graduate levels. As of 2018, bulletins for the SMFA are also included in this collection. Bulletins include school descriptions, admissions requirements, degree requirements, course descriptions, and rosters of faculty.
- Arts and Sciences, Engineering, and SMFA Bulletins, 1969 -- 2021; 1970 -- 2011; UP006.001; 42 Volumes; 44 Digital Object(s); 238.24 Megabytes Of the 44 digital objects in this series, 37 have extent information and comprise 238.24 MB.
  Scope and Contents
  A course bulletin for the Arts and Sciences published since 1969. Colleges that fall under the school are inconsistent but may include College of Liberal Arts, College of Engineering, College of Special Studies, Jackson School, Boston School of Occupational Therapy, Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, and the Museum School. See series 002 for the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences individual publication. Includes school descriptions, admissions requirements, degree requirements, course descriptions, and rosters of faculty. As of 2018, course bulletins for the SMFA are included in this series.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Undergraduate Colleges, 1969 -- 1970; UP006.001.00001 (Box data_value_missing_dfa1d264673cb67f5a4543627422fa70)
    College of Liberal Arts, College of Engineering, Jackson College, College of Special Studies
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Undergraduate Colleges, 1970 -- 1971; UP006.001.00002 (Box data_value_missing_e1795585b5ea9155c0f0d319b3a7c63c)
    Additional copy in reading room. College of Liberal Arts, College of Engineering, Jackson College, College of Special Studies.
  - Bulletin of Tufts University Undergraduate Colleges, 1971 -- 1972; UP006.001.00003 (Box data_value_missing_bf2efe168de50503493bc9bec1ab45a4)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1972 -- 1973; UP006.001.00004 (Box data_value_missing_e17aa68a3ea408f5e0ccb457eb16e846)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1973 -- 1974; UP006.001.00005 (Box data_value_missing_6d7f4dadd6e87585592c962f70da5dc6)
    College of Liberal Arts, College of Engineering, Jackson College, Graduate School
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1974 -- 1975; UP006.001.00006 (Box data_value_missing_c3d141b61c75ff6eb1d91a24157507a5)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1975 -- 1976; UP006.001.00007 (Box data_value_missing_11e8d71483eb46a76d5d0d26f2eda742)
  - Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1976 -- 1977; UP006.001.00008 (Box data_value_missing_fa60b8925f4af09c21e865aba79bc810)
    Additional copy in reading room. College of Liberal Arts, College of Engineering, Jackson College, Graduate School
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1977 -- 1978; UP006.001.00009 (Box data_value_missing_fcc683654ff18e44afe5d8e7ef729e50)
    Additional copy in reading room. College of Liberal Arts, College of Engineering, College of Special Studies, Jackson College, Graduate School
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1978 -- 1979; UP006.001.00010 (Box data_value_missing_b5878806c950ed69e8432b30810c46e3)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1979 -- 1980; UP006.001.00011 (Box data_value_missing_92fd09fb8f2cb9c166d0ad805cd1224d)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1980 -- 1981; UP006.001.00012 (Box data_value_missing_38fcfbd06f7ff397e2d3c7aa0e9a2037)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1981 -- 1982; UP006.001.00013 (Box data_value_missing_be2cb62110a0360c8c73535e6601c86b)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1982 -- 1983; UP006.001.00014 (Box data_value_missing_8e2b2be6e741fce9824fbfc2c230dea2)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1983 -- 1984; UP006.001.00015 (Box data_value_missing_7a6f6fb857d1914fa121ba85e9d4f367)
    Additional copy in reading room. Additional copy in reading room. College of Liberal Arts, College of Engineering, Jackson College, Boston School of Occupational Therapy, Graduate School, College of Special Studies.
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1984 -- 1985; UP006.001.00016 (Box data_value_missing_72ef141451bda93baae80616712cad33)
    Additional copy in reading room. College of Liberal Arts, College of Engineering, Jackson College, Boston School of Occupational Therapy, Graduate School, College of Special Studies
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1985 -- 1986; UP006.001.00017 (Box data_value_missing_e4a29e37d5f5f72a07e568ec8fcf9fa0)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1986 -- 1987; UP006.001.00018 (Box data_value_missing_9c66c4e917e7a43eba5abe013c451906)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1987 -- 1988; UP006.001.00019 (Box data_value_missing_edd91dca5653b345720dcba994b01d1d)
    Additional copy in reading room. College of Liberal Arts, Jackson College, College of Engineering, Boston School of Occupational Therapy, College of Special Studies, Graduate School
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1988 -- 1989; UP006.001.00020 (Box data_value_missing_7cbafc39f918c6b1077b8595613e31f1)
    Additional copy in reading room. College of Liberal Arts, College of Engineering, Boston School of Occupational Therapy, College of Special Studies, Graduate School
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1989 -- 1990; UP006.001.00021 (Box data_value_missing_8d1126e3faaea1a4f78733101a5ad1f4)
    Additional copy in reading room. College of Liberal Arts, College of Engineering, Boston School of Occupational Therapy, College of Special Studies, Graduate School of Arts and Sciences
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1990 -- 1991; UP006.001.00022 (Box data_value_missing_dbd882ff4acaf92b4baa7f277c8fae6e)
    Additional copy in reading room. College of Liberal Arts, College of Engineering, College of Special Studies, Graduate School of Arts and Sciences
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1991 -- 1992; UP006.001.00023 (Box data_value_missing_cd8e74711cc03265bd524c3d05b35d5e)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1992 -- 1993; UP006.001.00024 (Box data_value_missing_4e2d42330adbf1afa476109d18867045)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1993 -- 1994; UP006.001.00025 (Box data_value_missing_66bbedc4912e61fc4a4f698d27956db6)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1994 -- 1996; UP006.001.00026 (Box data_value_missing_d100ad96f2a3f9d78292d450518eba7c)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1996 -- 1998; UP006.001.00027 (Box data_value_missing_d9ec0b96de7dd9fb9c6ebbac7c0e8a0b)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University: Arts and Sciences, 1998 -- 2000; UP006.001.00028 (Box data_value_missing_a3412ffa026c0994e9f5f65cacb2ee71)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University, 2000 -- 2001; UP006.001.00029 (Box data_value_missing_78d876704508c6decc2b0509e0826eb1)
    Additional copy in reading room. School of Arts and Sciences (College of Liberal Arts, Graduate School of Arts and Sciences), School of Engineering
  - Bulletin of Tufts University, 2001 -- 2002; UP006.001.00030 (Box data_value_missing_03e08376049d0dbcdf6339a9e698880b)
    School of Arts and Sciences (College of Liberal Arts, Graduate School of Arts and Sciences), School of Engineering
  - Bulletin of Tufts University, 2002 -- 2003; UP006.001.00031 (Box data_value_missing_9fa10e32c4f42852d7dcf5602688b821)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University, 2003 -- 2004; UP006.001.00032 (Box data_value_missing_68a63f8b8d8809a3f3ee3446310babb7)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University, 2004 -- 2005; UP006.001.00033 (Box data_value_missing_8e356aefde0426cf6ad9f0f0c0c936be)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University, 2005 -- 2006; UP006.001.00034 (Box data_value_missing_ca484501ba6bb0ad7770d0a432dd4bcd)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University, 2006 -- 2007; UP006.001.00035 (Box data_value_missing_83c9347ab4f8cf2ef53659bf3f7178e5)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University, 2007 -- 2008; UP006.001.00036 (Box data_value_missing_3ff39177e362847498e00bc618ef0b75)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University, 2008 -- 2009; UP006.001.00037 (Box data_value_missing_8b408796b09cd7e5f580550bb98bb30f)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University, 2009 -- 2010; UP006.001.00038 (Box data_value_missing_9ec838df15cd4998673029cf8e66079f)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University, 2010 -- 2011; UP006.001.00039 (Box data_value_missing_19e68221d548c250ab663753de3aa1c9)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University, 2011 -- 2012; UP006.001.00040 (Box data_value_missing_1bc6c0304470f64504646419a511c3e5)
  - Bulletin of Tufts University, 2012 -- 2013; UP006.001.00041 (Box data_value_missing_da1a33875b742f931620c445e2e48e8f)
  - Africa in the New World interdisciplinary minor course listings, Spring 2013; UP006.000253; 1 Digital Object(s); 457 Kilobytes
  - Africa in the New World interdisciplinary minor course listings, Fall 2013; UP006.000252; 1 Digital Object(s); 791 Kilobytes
  - Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Fall 2013; UP006.000254; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.4 Megabytes
  - Engineering Bulletin, Fall 2013; UP006.000260; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.72 Megabytes
  - Bulletin of Tufts University, 2013 -- 2014; UP006.001.00042 (Box data_value_missing_fec9086cd229c9fdbc979067c090f66b)
    Additional copy in reading room. School of Arts and Sciences (College of Liberal Arts, Graduate School of Arts and Sciences), School of Engineering.
  - Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Spring 2014; UP006.000257; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.2 Megabytes
  - Engineering Bulletin, Spring 2014; UP006.000263; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.54 Megabytes
  - Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Fall 2014; UP006.000255; 1 Digital Object(s); 12 Megabytes
  - Engineering Bulletin, Fall 2014; UP006.000261; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.89 Megabytes
  - Bulletin of Tufts University, 2014 -- 2015; UP006.001.00052.000001 (Volume 52)
    School of Arts and Sciences (College of Liberal Arts, Graduate School of Arts and Sciences), School of Engineering.
  - Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Spring 2015; UP006.000258; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.1 Megabytes
  - Engineering Bulletin, Spring 2015; UP006.000264; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.89 Megabytes
  - Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Fall 2015; UP006.000256; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.1 Megabytes
  - Engineering Bulletin, Fall 2015; UP006.000262; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.85 Megabytes
  - Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Spring 2016; UP006.000259; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.4 Megabytes
  - Engineering Bulletin, Spring 2016; UP006.000265; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.89 Megabytes
  - Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Fall 2016; UP006.001.00043; School of Arts and Sciences; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.67 Megabytes
    Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Fall 2016
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Transferred by Tufts Technology Services, 2016, accession 2017.022.
  - Engineering Bulletin, Fall 2016; UP006.001.00044; School of Engineering; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.76 Megabytes
    Engineering Bulletin, Fall 2016
  - Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Spring 2017; UP006.001.00045; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.07 Megabytes
    Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Spring 2017
    Transferred by Tufts Technology Services, 2017, accession UP-2018-012.
  - Engineering Bulletin, Spring 2017; UP006.001.00046; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.87 Megabytes
    Engineering Bulletin, Spring 2017
  - Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Fall 2017; UP006.001.00047; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.07 Megabytes
    Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Fall 2017
  - Engineering Bulletin, Fall 2017; UP006.001.00048; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.76 Megabytes
    Engineering Bulletin, Fall 2017
  - Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Spring 2018; UP006.001.00049; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.02 Megabytes
    Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Spring 2018
    Transferred by Tufts Technology Services, 2018, accession UP-2018-033.
  - Engineering Bulletin, Spring 2018; UP006.001.00050; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.95 Megabytes
    Engineering Bulletin, Spring 2018
  - SMFA Bulletin, Spring 2018; UP006.001.00051; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.85 Megabytes
    SMFA Bulletin, Spring 2018
  - Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Fall 2018; UP006.001.00052.000002; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.95 Megabytes
    Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Fall 2018
  - Engineering Bulletin, Fall 2018; UP006.001.00053; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.29 Megabytes
    Engineering Bulletin, Fall 2018
  - SMFA Bulletin, Fall 2018; UP006.001.00054; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.64 Megabytes
    SMFA Bulletin, Fall 2018
  - Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Spring 2019; UP006.001.00055; 1 Digital Object(s); 12.44 Megabytes
    Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Spring 2019
  - Engineering Bulletin, Spring 2019; UP006.001.00056; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.1 Megabytes
    Engineering Bulletin, Spring 2019
  - Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Fall 2019; UP006.000246
    Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Fall 2019
  - Engineering Bulletin, Fall 2019; UP006.000251
    Engineering Bulletin, Fall 2019
  - SMFA Bulletin, Fall 2019; UP006.000248
    SMFA Bulletin, Fall 2019
  - Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Spring 2020; UP006.000249
    Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Spring 2020
  - Engineering Bulletin, Spring 2020; UP006.000250
    Engineering Bulletin, Spring 2020
  - Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Fall 2020; UP006.000266; 14.5 Megabytes
    Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Fall 2020
  - Engineering Bulletin, Fall 2020; UP006.000267; 2.95 Megabytes
    Engineering Bulletin, Fall 2020
  - Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Spring 2021; UP006.000269; 17.23 Megabytes
  - Engineering Bulletin, Spring 2021; UP006.000270; 3.03 Megabytes
  - Museum School Bulletin, Spring 2021; UP006.000271; 3.18 Megabytes
  - Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Fall 2021; UP006.000273; 14.62 Megabytes
  - Arts and Sciences Online Bulletin, Fall 2021; UP006.000274; 215.38 Kilobytes
  - Engineering Bulletin, Fall 2021; UP006.000275; 3.12 Megabytes
  - Engineering Online Bulletin, Fall 2021; UP006.000276; 630.49 Kilobytes
  - Museum School Bulletin, Fall 2021; UP006.000277; 3.1 Megabytes
  - Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Spring 2022; UP006.000286; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.4 Megabytes
  - Arts and Sciences Online Bulletin, Spring 2022; UP006.000285; 1 Digital Object(s); 184 Kilobytes
  - Engineering Bulletin, Spring 2022; UP006.000284; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.58 Megabytes
  - Engineering Online Bulletin, Spring 2022; UP006.000283; 1 Digital Object(s); 176 Kilobytes
  - SMFA Bulletin, Spring 2022; UP006.000287; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.98 Megabytes
  - Arts and Sciences Bulletin, Fall 2022; UP006.000281; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.38 Megabytes
  - Arts and Sciences Online Bulletin, Fall 2022; UP006.000282; 1 Digital Object(s); 226 Kilobytes
  - Engineering Bulletin, Fall 2022; UP006.000279; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.63 Megabytes
  - Engineering Online Bulletin, Fall 2022; UP006.000280; 1 Digital Object(s); 207 Kilobytes
- Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Bulletin, 1969 -- 1983; 1969 -- 2021; UP006.002; 14 Volumes; 3 Digital Object(s); 1.35 Megabytes
  A course bulletin for the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences published since 1969. Includes school description, admission requirements, degree requirements, and course descriptions.
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1969 -- 1970; UP006.002.00001 (Box data_value_missing_03dc80d5f4b2a177c83faf4e17dce649)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1970 -- 1971; UP006.002.00002 (Box data_value_missing_8e661eafe00dbb0c3512e34f4d9f85ba)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1971 -- 1972; UP006.002.00003 (Box data_value_missing_7a901b4dfaa9ccf3ca2cdaffb1fc0a3d)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1972 -- 1973; UP006.002.00004 (Box data_value_missing_1c00ee33498c72da9a891cb29d8b0ad0)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1973 -- 1974; UP006.002.00005 (Box data_value_missing_c18b17ceef9bf17cd538d298d16fb8c5)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1974 -- 1975; UP006.002.00006 (Box data_value_missing_ed95f7701ff2ea1caf949be506602ef1)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1975 -- 1976; UP006.002.00007 (Box data_value_missing_2a280da4d0d7c31fd90179c3ce0acf10)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1976 -- 1977; UP006.002.00008 (Box data_value_missing_6496b61987958c8dd7bb2670f80cc1cc)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1977 -- 1978; UP006.002.00009 (Box data_value_missing_2e913e083ca603823211d3bb9bda469f)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1978 -- 1979; UP006.002.00010 (Box data_value_missing_89536cfc640716a58bb107e0489624f8)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1979 -- 1980; UP006.002.00011 (Box data_value_missing_d1b934a303864eddac66bb0ac617819f)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1980 -- 1981; UP006.002.00012 (Box data_value_missing_5dff2c6ee699fdb627d41788f6aa464e)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1981 -- 1982; UP006.002.00013 (Box data_value_missing_7ab2cf3ba2aad8fa58084ed8e633fbc6)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1982 -- 1983; UP006.002.00014 (Box data_value_missing_2fcd7133b9967d5e7f8b53626c4e6b64)
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering Graduate Online Program, Spring 2020; UP006.000247
    Arts, Sciences and Engineering Graduate Online Program, Fall 2019
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering Graduate Online Program, Fall 2020; UP006.000268; 603 Kilobytes
    Arts, Sciences and Engineering Graduate Online Program, Fall 2020
  - Arts, Sciences and Engineering Graduate Online Program, Spring 2021; UP006.000272; 638.19 Kilobytes
- Announcement of Courses and Course Descriptions, 1943 -- 2012; UP006.003; 1.5 Linear Feet
  Announcement of Courses is a supplement to the University Catalog, providing a revised list of classes and time-blocks.
  - Announcement of Courses, 1943-06-01; UP006.003.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, November Term, 1943; UP006.003.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, March Term, 1944; UP006.003.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, July Term, 1944; UP006.003.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, November Term, 1944; UP006.003.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, March Term, 1945; UP006.003.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, Summer Term, 1945; UP006.003.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, November Term, 1945; UP006.003.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, March Term, 1946; UP006.003.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall Term, 1946; UP006.003.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring Term, 1947; UP006.003.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall and Spring Terms, 1947 -- 1948; UP006.003.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall and Spring Terms, 1948 -- 1949; UP006.003.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall and Spring Terms, 1949 -- 1950; UP006.003.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall and Spring Terms, 1950 -- 1951; UP006.003.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall and Spring Terms, 1951 -- 1952; UP006.003.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall and Spring Terms, 1952 -- 1953; UP006.003.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses Number, 1953 -- 1954; UP006.003.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses Number, 1954 -- 1955; UP006.003.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, 1955 -- 1956; UP006.003.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, 1956 -- 1957; UP006.003.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, 1957 -- 1958; UP006.003.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, 1958 -- 1959; UP006.003.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Spring Term Course List, 1959; UP006.003.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, 1959 -- 1960; UP006.003.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, 1960 -- 1961; UP006.003.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, 1961 -- 1962; UP006.003.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, 1962 -- 1963; UP006.003.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, 1963 -- 1964; UP006.003.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, 1964 -- 1965; UP006.003.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, 1965 -- 1966; UP006.003.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, 1966 -- 1967; UP006.003.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, 1967 -- 1968; UP006.003.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1968 -- 1969; UP006.003.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1969; UP006.003.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - Freshman Supplement, 1968 -- 1969; UP006.003.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1969; UP006.003.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1970; UP006.003.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1970; UP006.003.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1971; UP006.003.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1972; UP006.003.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1972; UP006.003.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1973; UP006.003.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1973; UP006.003.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1974; UP006.003.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1974; UP006.003.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1975; UP006.003.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1975; UP006.003.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1976; UP006.003.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1976; UP006.003.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1977; UP006.003.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1977; UP006.003.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1978; UP006.003.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1978; UP006.003.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1979; UP006.003.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1979; UP006.003.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1980; UP006.003.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1980; UP006.003.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1981; UP006.003.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Tufts Summer School, 1981; UP006.003.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1981; UP006.003.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1982; UP006.003.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1982; UP006.003.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1983; UP006.003.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1983; UP006.003.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1984; UP006.003.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1984; UP006.003.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1985; UP006.003.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1985; UP006.003.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1986; UP006.003.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Fall, 1986; UP006.003.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - Announcement of Courses, Spring, 1987; UP006.003.003.00001 (Box 3)